A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1924-1939 FA308
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1935
  - China, 1935; 1935/601
    - China - Public Health Demonstrations, 1935; 1935/601.J
      - China, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 943)
  - Japan, 1935; 1935/609
    - Japan, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 943)
    - Japan, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 944)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/609.E
      - Japan, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 944)
    - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1935; 1935/609.R
      - Japan, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 944)
  - Thailand, 1935; 1935/617
    - Thailand, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 945)
    - Thailand - Nursing, 1935; 1935/617.C
      - Thailand, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 945)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/617.E
      - Thailand, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 945)
  - Holland, 1935; 1935/650
    - Netherlands, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 946)
    - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 946)
    - Holland - Social Sciences, 1935; 1935/650.S
      - Netherlands, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 946)
  - Europe, 1935; 1935/700
    - Europe - (A-L), 1935 (Box 125, Folder 947)
    - Europe - (M-R), 1935 (Box 125, Folder 948)
    - Europe - Strode, George K., 1935 (Box 125, Folder 949)
    - Europe - (T-Z), 1935 (Box 126, Folder 950)
    - Europe - Social Sciences, 1935; 1935/700.S
      - Europe, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 950)
  - Austria, 1935; 1935/705
    - Austria, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 951)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/705.E
      - Austria, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 951)
  - Balkan States, 1935; 1935/706
    - SMI-1 Smillie, Wilson G. "Report of a Brief Visit to the Activities of the IHD in the Balkan States", 1935 (Box 559, Folder 3794)
  - Belgium, 1935; 1935/707
    - Belgium, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 951)
    - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/707.E
      - Belgium, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 951)
  - Yugoslavia, 1935; 1935/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 951)
  - Bulgaria, 1935; 1935/711
    - Bulgaria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/711.E
      - Bulgaria, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 951)
    - Bulgaria - Social Sciences, 1935; 1935/711.S
      - Bulgaria, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 951)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1935; 1935/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 951)
    - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/712.E
      - Czechoslovakia, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 951)
  - Germany, 1935; 1935/717
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars - (Baehr Committee), 1935 (Box 126, Folder 952)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars - (Murrow Committee), 1935 (Box 126, Folder 953)
    - Germany - (A-P), 1935 (Box 126, Folder 954)
    - Germany - (R-Z), 1935 (Box 126, Folder 955)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars, 1935 (Box 549, Folder 3660)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1935; 1935/717.D
      - Germany, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 955)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/717.E
      - Germany, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 955)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1935; 1935/717.S
      - Germany, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 955)
  - Hungary, 1935; 1935/750
    - Hungary, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 956)
    - Hungary - Social Sciences, 1935; 1935/750.S
      - Hungary, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 956)
  - Italy, 1935; 1935/751
    - Italy, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 956)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/751.E
      - Italy, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
    - Italy - Public Health Education, 1935; 1935/751.L
      - Italy, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1935; 1935/751.S
      - Italy, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
  - Norway, 1935; 1935/767
    - Norway, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/767.E
      - Norway, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
  - Portugal, 1935; 1935/773
    - Portugal, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
    - Portugal - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/773.E
      - Portugal, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
  - Romania, 1935; 1935/783
    - Romania, 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
  - USSR, 1935; 1935/785
    - U.S.S.R., 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
    - USSR - Medical Sciences, 1935; 1935/785.A
      - U.S.S.R., 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
    - USSR - Social Sciences, 1935; 1935/785.S
      - U.S.S.R., 1935 (Box 126, Folder 957)
  - Latvia, 1935; 1935/786
    - Latvia, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 958)
    - Latvia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/786.E
      - Latvia, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 958)
  - Finland, 1935; 1935/787
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/787.E
      - Finland, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 958)
  - Lithuania, 1935; 1935/788
    - Lithuania, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 958)
    - Lithuania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/788.E
      - Lithuania, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 958)
  - Poland, 1935; 1935/789
    - Poland, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 958)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/789.E
      - Poland, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 958)
  - Sweden, 1935; 1935/800
    - Sweden, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 958)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/800.E
      - Sweden, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 958)
  - Switzerland, 1935; 1935/803
    - Switzerland, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 959)
    - Switzerland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1935; 1935/803.D
      - Switzerland, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 959)
    - Switzerland - Social Sciences, 1935; 1935/803.S
      - Switzerland, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 959)
  - Turkey, 1935; 1935/805
    - Turkey, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 959)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/805.E
      - Turkey, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 959)
  - Crete, 1935; 1935/807
    - Crete, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 959)
  - Cyprus, 1935; 1935/809
    - Cyrus, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 959)
  - Lebanon, 1935; 1935/833
    - Lebanon, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 959)
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1935; 1935/833.E
      - Lebanon, 1935 (Box 127, Folder 959)
- General Correspondence, 1936
  - International, 1936; 1936/100
    - (A-K), 1936 (Box 127, Folder 960)
    - (R-S), 1936 (Box 127, Folder 961)
    - (S-Z), 1936 (Box 127, Folder 962)
    - International - Malaria, 1936; 1936/100.I
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1936 (Box 127, Folder 962)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1936; 1936/100.O
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1936 (Box 127, Folder 962)
    - International - Humanities and Arts, 1936; 1936/100.R
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1936 (Box 127, Folder 962)
    - International - Tuberculosis, 1936; 1936/100.T
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1936 (Box 127, Folder 962)
  - United States, 1936; 1936/200
    - United States - (A), 1936 (Box 127, Folder 963)
    - United States - (B), 1936 (Box 127, Folder 964)
    - United States - (C-Co), 1936 (Box 128, Folder 965)
    - United States - Cook, Thomas and Son, 1936 (Box 128, Folder 966)
    - United States - Cook, Thomas and Son - (Co), 1936 (Box 128, Folder 967)
    - United States - Covington, P. W., 1936 (Box 128, Folder 968)
    - United States - (Co-F), 1936 (Box 128, Folder 969)
    - United States - (G), 1936 (Box 128, Folder 970)
    - United States - (H-In), 1936 (Box 129, Folder 971)
    - United States - (In-Iz), 1936 (Box 129, Folder 972)
    - United States - (J-L), 1936 (Box 129, Folder 973)
    - United States - (M-Ma), 1936 (Box 129, Folder 974)
    - United States - (Ma-Mz), 1936 (Box 129, Folder 975)
    - United States - (N-O), 1936 (Box 129, Folder 976)
    - United States - (P-Sm), 1936 (Box 130, Folder 977)
    - United States - (So-T), 1936 (Box 130, Folder 978)
    - United States - (U-V), 1936 (Box 130, Folder 979)
    - United States - (W-Z), 1936 (Box 130, Folder 980)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1936; 1936/200.A
      - United States, 1936 (Box 130, Folder 981)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1936; 1936/200.D
      - United States, 1936 (Box 130, Folder 981)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/200.E
      - United States, 1936 (Box 130, Folder 981)
    - United States - Public Health Education, 1936; 1936/200.L
      - United States, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 982)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1936; 1936/200.R
      - United States, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 982)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/200.S
      - United States, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 982)
  - Alabama, 1936; 1936/201
    - Alabama, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 983)
    - Alabama - Public Health Education, 1936; 1936/201.L
      - Alabama, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 983)
  - Arizona, 1936; 1936/203
    - Arizona, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 983)
  - Arkansas, 1936; 1936/204
    - Arkansas, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 983)
  - California, 1936; 1936/205
    - California, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 983)
    - California - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/205.E
      - California, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 983)
    - California - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/205.S
      - California, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 983)
  - Colorado, 1936; 1936/207
    - Colorado, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 984)
  - District of Columbia, 1936; 1936/210
    - District of Columbia, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 984)
  - Florida, 1936; 1936/211
    - Florida, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 984)
    - Florida - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/211.E
      - Florida, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 984)
  - Georgia, 1936; 1936/212
    - Georgia, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 984)
  - Hawaii, 1936; 1936/214
    - Hawaii, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 984)
  - Idaho, 1936; 1936/215
    - Idaho, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 985)
  - Illinois, 1936; 1936/216
    - Illinois, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 985)
  - Iowa, 1936; 1936/218
    - Iowa, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 985)
    - Iowa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/218.E
      - Iowa, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 985)
  - Kansas, 1936; 1936/219
    - Kansas, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 986)
  - Kentucky, 1936; 1936/220
    - Kentucky, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 986)
  - Maine, 1936; 1936/222
    - Maine - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/222.E
      - Maine, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 986)
  - Maryland, 1936; 1936/223
    - Maryland, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 987)
  - Massachusetts, 1936; 1936/224
    - Massachusetts, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 988)
    - Massachusetts - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1936; 1936/224.D
      - Massachusetts, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 988)
    - Massachusetts - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/224.E
      - Massachusetts, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 988)
  - Michigan, 1936; 1936/225
    - Michigan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/225.E
      - Michigan, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 988)
  - Mississippi, 1936; 1936/227
    - Mississippi, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 988)
    - Mississippi - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/227.E
      - Mississippi, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 988)
  - Missouri, 1936; 1936/228
    - Missouri, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 989)
  - Montana, 1936; 1936/229
    - Montana, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 989)
  - Nevada, 1936; 1936/231
    - Nevada, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 989)
  - New Hampshire, 1936; 1936/232
    - New Hampshire, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 989)
  - New Mexico, 1936; 1936/234
    - New Mexico, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 989)
  - North Carolina, 1936; 1936/236
    - North Carolina, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 990)
    - North Carolina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/236.E
      - North Carolina, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 990)
  - North Dakota, 1936; 1936/237
    - North Dakota, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 991)
  - Ohio, 1936; 1936/238
    - Ohio, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 991)
    - Ohio - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/238.E
      - Ohio, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 991)
  - Oregon, 1936; 1936/240
    - Oregon, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 991)
  - Pennsylvania, 1936; 1936/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 992)
    - Pennsylvania - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1936; 1936/241.D
      - Pennsylvania, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 992)
  - Rhode Island, 1936; 1936/244
    - Rhode Island, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 992)
  - South Carolina, 1936; 1936/246
    - South Carolina, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 992)
    - South Carolina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/246.E
      - South Carolina, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 992)
  - South Dakota, 1936; 1936/247
    - South Dakota, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 992)
    - South Dakota - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/247.E
      - South Dakota, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 992)
  - Tennessee, 1936; 1936/248
    - Tennessee, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 993)
  - Texas, 1936; 1936/249
    - Texas, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 994)
  - Utah, 1936; 1936/250
    - Utah, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 994)
    - Utah - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/250.E
      - Utah, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 994)
  - Virginia, 1936; 1936/252
    - Virginia, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 994)
    - Virginia, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 995)
    - Virginia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/252.E
      - Virginia, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 995)
  - Washington, 1936; 1936/253
    - Washington, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 995)
    - Washington - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/253.E
      - Washington, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 995)
  - West Virginia, 1936; 1936/254
    - West Virginia, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 995)
  - Wisconsin, 1936; 1936/255
    - Wisconsin, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 996)
  - Wyoming, 1936; 1936/256
    - Wyoming, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 996)
  - Virgin Islands, 1936; 1936/257
    - Virgin Islands, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 996)
  - Latin America, 1936; 1936/300
    - Latin America, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 997)
    - Latin America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/300.E
      - Latin America, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 997)
  - Argentina, 1936; 1936/301
    - Argentina, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 997)
    - Argentina - Yellow Fever, 1936; 1936/301.O
      - Argentina, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 997)
  - Bolivia, 1936; 1936/303
    - Bolivia, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 997)
  - Brazil, 1936; 1936/305
    - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1936; 1936/305.O
      - YEA-1 Yeager, Clark N. "Jungle Yellow Fever in the Sao Joao dos Patos Regions", 1936 (Box 559, Folder 3795)
  - Chile, 1936; 1936/309
    - Chile, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 997)
  - Colombia, 1936; 1936/311
    - Colombia, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 998)
    - Colombia - Nursing, 1936; 1936/311.C
      - Colombia, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 998)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/311.E
      - Colombia, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 998)
  - Costa Rica, 1936; 1936/313
    - Costa Rica, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 998)
    - Costa Rica - Public Health Demonstrations, 1936; 1936/313.J
      - Costa Rica, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 998)
    - Costa Rica - Health Services, 1936; 1936/313.K
      - MOL-1 Molloy, Daniel M. "Making of Cement Latrine Fixtures for the All-Concrete Privy Used in Costa Rica", 1936 (Box 559, Folder 3796)
    - Costa Rica - Public Health Education, 1936; 1936/313.L
      - Costa Rica, 1936 (Box 133, Folder 998)
  - Cuba, 1936; 1936/315
    - Cuba - (A-Z), 1936 (Box 133, Folder 999)
    - Cuba - Carr, Henry P., 1936 (Box 133, Folder 1000)
    - Cuba - Carr, Henry P., 1936 (Box 134, Folder 1001)
    - Cuba - Carr, Henry P., 1936 (Box 134, Folder 1002)
    - Cuba - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/315.E
      - Cuba, 1936 (Box 134, Folder 1002)
  - Guatemala, 1936; 1936/319
    - Guatemala, 1936 (Box 134, Folder 1003)
    - Guatemala - Public Health Education, 1936; 1936/319.L
      - Guatemala, 1936 (Box 134, Folder 1003)
  - Mexico, 1936; 02.1936/323
    - Mexico - Administration, 1936 (Box 134, Folder 1004-1005)
    - Mexico - Bailey, Charles A., 1936 (Box 134, Folder 1006-1007)
    - Mexico - (B-Z), 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1008)
    - Mexico - Nursing, 1936; 1936/323.C
      - Mexico, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1008)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/323.E
      - Mexico, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1008)
  - Nicaragua, 1936; 1936/325
    - Nicaragua, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
    - Nicaragua - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/325.E
      - Nicaragua, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
    - Nicaragua - Malaria, 1936; 1936/325.I
      - Nicaragua, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
  - Panama, 1936; 1936/327
    - Panama, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
    - Panama - Nursing, 1936; 1936/327.C
      - Panama, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
    - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/327.E
      - Panama, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
    - Panama - Public Health Education, 1936; 1936/327.L
      - Panama, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
    - Panama - Tuberculosis, 1936; 1936/327.T
      - Panama, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
  - El Salvador, 1936; 1936/333
    - El Salvador, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
    - El Salvador - Nursing, 1936; 1936/333.C
      - El Salvador, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
    - El Salvador - Public Health Demonstrations, 1936; 1936/333.J
      - El Salvador, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
  - Uruguay, 1936; 1936/337
    - Uruguay, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1009)
  - Venezuela, 1936; 1936/339
    - Venezuela - Health, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1010)
    - Venezuela - Health - (A-Z) - Health Program, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1011)
    - Venezuela, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1012)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1012)
    - Venezuela - Health Services, 1936; 1936/339.K
      - Venezuela, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1012)
  - England, 1936; 1936/401
    - England - (A-M), 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1012)
    - England - (N-Z), 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1013)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1936; 1936/401.A
      - England, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1013)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/401.E
      - England, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1013)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/401.S
      - England, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 1013)
  - Scotland, 1936; 1936/405
    - Scotland, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
  - Australia, 1936; 1936/410
    - Australia, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1936; 1936/410.A
      - Australia, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/410.E
      - Australia, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
    - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1936; 1936/410.R
      - Australia, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
    - Australia - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/410.S
      - Australia, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
  - New Zealand, 1936; 1936/418
    - New Zealand, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/418.E
      - New Zealand (Box 136, Folder 1014)
    - New Zealand - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/418.S
      - New Zealand (Box 136, Folder 1014)
  - Fiji, 1936; 1936/419
    - Fiji, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
    - Fiji - Nursing, 1936; 1936/419.C
      - Fiji, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
    - Fiji - Public Health Demonstrations, 1936; 1936/419.J
      - Fiji, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1014)
  - Caribbean Area, 1936; 1936/420
    - Caribbean Area, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1015)
    - Caribbean Area - Nursing, 1936; 1936/420.C
      - Caribbean Area, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1015)
  - Belize, 1936; 1936/425
    - British Honduras, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1015)
  - Canada, 1936; 1936/427
    - Canada, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1016)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1936; 1936/427.A
      - Canada, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1016)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/427.E
      - Canada, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1016)
    - Canada - Public Health Educations, 1936; 1936/427.L
      - Canada, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1016)
  - Jamaica, 1936; 1936/437
    - Jamaica - (A-R), 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1017)
    - Jamaica - Saunders, George M., 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1018)
    - Jamaica - Washburn, B. E., 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1019)
    - Jamaica - Washburn, B. E., 1936 (Box 136, Folder 1020)
    - Jamaica - Washburn, B. E., 1936 (Box 137, Folder 1021)
  - India, 1936; 02.1936/464
    - India - Administration, 1936 (Box 137, Folder 1022)
    - India - Administration - (B-E), 1936 (Box 137, Folder 1023)
    - India - Jacocks, W. P., 1936 (Box 137, Folder 1024)
    - India - Jacocks, W. P., 1936 (Box 137, Folder 1025)
    - India - (K-P), 1936 (Box 137, Folder 1026)
    - India - Russell, Paul F., 1936 (Box 137, Folder 1027)
    - India - Russell, Paul F., 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1028)
    - India - Russell, Paul F. - Russell Publications - (S), 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1029)
    - India - Sweet, W. C. - Sweet Publications, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1030)
    - India - Nursing, 1936; 1936/464.C
      - India, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1031)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/464.E
      - India, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1031)
    - India - Public Health Education, 1936; 1936/464.L
      - India, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1031)
    - India - Mysore, 1936; 1936/464.1
      - India - (Mysore), 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1031)
    - India - Travancore, 1936; 1936/464.5
      - India - (Travancore), 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1031)
  - Bengal, 1936; 1936/466
    - Bengal, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1031)
  - Africa, 1936; 1936/475
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/475.S
      - Africa, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1031)
  - North Africa Region, 1936; 1936/485
    - Egypt, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1031)
    - Egypt - Barlow, C. H. - Barlow Publications, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1032)
    - North Africa Region - Yellow Fever, 1936; 1936/485.O
      - Egypt, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1033)
  - South Africa, 1936; 1936/487
    - South Africa, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1033)
  - France, 1936; 1936/500
    - France, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1033)
    - France - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1936; 1936/500.D
      - France, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1033)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/500.E
      - France, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1033)
  - Asia, 1936; 1936/600
    - HYD-1 Hydrick, John L. "Observations re Public Health Visits", 1936 (Box 559, Folder 3797)
    - Asia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/600.E
      - Asia, 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1033)
  - China, 1936; 1936/601
    - China - (A-C), 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1034)
    - China - (D-G), 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1035)
    - China - (H-P), 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1036)
    - China - (R-Z), 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1037)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1936; 1936/601.A
      - China, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1037)
    - China - Nursing, 1936; 1936/601.C
      - China, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1037)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/601.E
      - China, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1037)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1936; 1936/601.R
      - China, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1037)
    - China - Yaws, 1936; 1936/601.U
      - China, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1037)
  - Japan, 1936; 1936/609
    - Japan - (A-Z), 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1038)
  - Thailand, 1936; 1936/617
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/617.E
      - Thailand - Atrikesar, Sa-ing, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1039)
  - Holland, 1936; 1936/650
    - Netherlands, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1040)
    - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1040)
    - Holland - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/650.S
      - Netherlands, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1040)
  - Europe, 1936; 1936/700
    - Europe - (A-K), 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1040)
    - Europe - (L-O), 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1041)